<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<recipes><recipe><id>52772</id><title>Teriyaki Chicken Casserole</title><ingredients><ingredient><quantity>3/4</quantity><unit>cup soy sauce</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/2</quantity><unit>cup water</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/4</quantity><unit>cup brown sugar</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/2</quantity><unit>teaspoon ground ginger</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/2</quantity><unit>teaspoon minced garlic</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>4</quantity><unit>Tablespoons cornstarch</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>chicken breasts</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>(12 oz.) stir-fry vegetables</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>3</quantity><unit>cups brown rice</unit><item /></ingredient></ingredients><instructions>&lt;action&gt;Preheat&lt;/action&gt; oven to 350° F. Spray a 9x13-inch baking pan with non-stick spray.
Combine soy sauce, ½ cup water, brown sugar, ginger and garlic in a small saucepan and cover. Bring to a &lt;action&gt;boil&lt;/action&gt; over medium &lt;action&gt;heat&lt;/action&gt;. Remove lid and &lt;action&gt;cook&lt;/action&gt; for one minute once boiling.
Meanwhile, &lt;action&gt;stir&lt;/action&gt; together the corn starch and 2 tablespoons of water in a separate dish until smooth. Once sauce is boiling, &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; mixture to the saucepan and &lt;action&gt;stir&lt;/action&gt; to combine. &lt;action&gt;Cook&lt;/action&gt; until the sauce starts to thicken then remove from &lt;action&gt;heat&lt;/action&gt;.
Place the chicken breasts in the prepared pan. &lt;action&gt;Pour&lt;/action&gt; one cup of the sauce over top of chicken. Place chicken in oven and &lt;action&gt;bake&lt;/action&gt; 35 minutes or until cooked through. Remove from oven and shred chicken in the dish using two forks.
*Meanwhile, steam or &lt;action&gt;cook&lt;/action&gt; the vegetables according to package directions.
&lt;action&gt;Add&lt;/action&gt; the cooked vegetables and rice to the casserole dish with the chicken. &lt;action&gt;Add&lt;/action&gt; most of the remaining sauce, reserving a bit to drizzle over the top when serving. Gently toss everything together in the casserole dish until combined. Return to oven and &lt;action&gt;cook&lt;/action&gt; 15 minutes. Remove from oven and let stand 5 minutes before serving. Drizzle each serving with remaining sauce. Enjoy!</instructions></recipe><recipe><id>52874</id><title>Beef and Mustard Pie</title><ingredients><ingredient><quantity /><unit>1kg Beef</unit><item>1kg Beef</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>tbs Plain Flour</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>tbs Rapeseed Oil</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>200ml Red Wine</unit><item>200ml Red Wine</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>400ml Beef Stock</unit><item>400ml Beef Stock</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>finely sliced Onion</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>chopped Carrots</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>3</quantity><unit>sprigs Thyme</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>tbs Mustard</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>free-range Egg Yolks</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>400g Puff Pastry</unit><item>400g Puff Pastry</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>300g Green Beans</unit><item>300g Green Beans</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>25g Butter</unit><item>25g Butter</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>pinch Salt</unit><item>pinch Salt</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>pinch Pepper</unit><item>pinch Pepper</item></ingredient></ingredients><instructions>&lt;action&gt;Preheat&lt;/action&gt; the oven to 150C/300F/Gas 2.
Toss the beef and flour together in a bowl with some salt and black pepper.
&lt;action&gt;Heat&lt;/action&gt; a large casserole until hot, &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; half of the rapeseed oil and enough of the beef to just cover the bottom of the casserole.
&lt;action&gt;Fry&lt;/action&gt; until browned on each side, then remove and set aside. Repeat with the remaining oil and beef.
Return the beef to the pan, &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; the wine and &lt;action&gt;cook&lt;/action&gt; until the volume of liquid has reduced by half, then &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; the stock, onion, carrots, thyme and mustard, and &lt;action&gt;season&lt;/action&gt; well with salt and pepper.
Cover with a lid and place in the oven for two hours.
Remove from the oven, check the seasoning and set aside to cool. Remove the thyme.
When the beef is cool and you're ready to assemble the pie, &lt;action&gt;preheat&lt;/action&gt; the oven to 200C/400F/Gas 6.
Transfer the beef to a pie dish, brush the rim with the beaten egg yolks and lay the pastry over the top. Brush the top of the pastry with more beaten egg.
Trim the pastry so there is just enough excess to crimp the edges, then place in the oven and &lt;action&gt;bake&lt;/action&gt; for 30 minutes, or until the pastry is golden-brown and cooked through.
For the green beans, bring a saucepan of salted water to the &lt;action&gt;boil&lt;/action&gt;, &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; the beans and &lt;action&gt;cook&lt;/action&gt; for 4-5 minutes, or until just tender.
Drain and toss with the butter, then &lt;action&gt;season&lt;/action&gt; with black pepper.
To serve, place a large spoonful of pie onto each plate with some green beans alongside.</instructions></recipe><recipe><id>52928</id><title>BeaverTails</title><ingredients><ingredient><quantity>1/2</quantity><unit>cup Water</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>parts Yeast</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/2</quantity><unit>cup Sugar</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/2</quantity><unit>cup Milk</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>6</quantity><unit>tblsp Butter</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>Eggs</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>½ tsp Salt</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>2-1/2 cups Flour</unit><item>2-1/2 cups Flour</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>for frying Oil</unit><item>for frying Oil</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>garnish Lemon</unit><item>garnish Lemon</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>garnish Sugar</unit><item>garnish Sugar</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>garnish Cinnamon</unit><item>garnish Cinnamon</item></ingredient></ingredients><instructions>In the bowl of a stand mixer, &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; warm water, a big pinch of sugar and yeast. Allow to sit until frothy.
Into the same bowl, &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; 1/2 cup sugar, warm milk, melted butter, eggs and salt, and &lt;action&gt;whisk&lt;/action&gt; until combined.
Place a dough hook on the mixer, &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; the flour with the machine on, until a smooth but slightly sticky dough forms.
Place dough in a bowl, cover with plastic wrap, and allow to proof for 1 1/2 hours.
Cut dough into 12 pieces, and roll out into long oval-like shapes about 1/4 inch thick that resemble a beaver’s tail.
In a large, deep pot, &lt;action&gt;heat&lt;/action&gt; oil to 350 degrees. Gently place beavertail dough into hot oil and &lt;action&gt;cook&lt;/action&gt; for 30 to 45 seconds on each side until golden brown.
Drain on paper towels, and garnish as desired. Toss in cinnamon sugar, in white sugar with a squeeze of lemon, or with a generous slathering of Nutella and a handful of toasted almonds. Enjoy!</instructions></recipe><recipe><id>53013</id><title>Big Mac</title><ingredients><ingredient><quantity /><unit>400g Minced Beef</unit><item>400g Minced Beef</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>tbs Olive Oil</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>Sesame Seed Burger Buns</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>Chopped Onion</unit><item>Chopped Onion</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/4</quantity><unit>Iceberg Lettuce</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>sliced Cheese</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>large Dill Pickles</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>cup Mayonnaise</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>tsp White Wine Vinegar</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>Pinch Pepper</unit><item>Pinch Pepper</item></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>tsp Mustard</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>1/2 tsp Onion Salt</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>1/2 tsp Garlic Powder</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/2</quantity><unit>tsp Paprika</unit><item /></ingredient></ingredients><instructions>For the Big Mac sauce, combine all the ingredients in a bowl, &lt;action&gt;season&lt;/action&gt; with salt and chill until ready to use.
2. To make the patties, &lt;action&gt;season&lt;/action&gt; the mince with salt and pepper and form into 4 balls using about 1/3 cup mince each. Place each onto a square of baking paper and flatten to form into four x 15cm circles. &lt;action&gt;Heat&lt;/action&gt; oil in a large frypan over high &lt;action&gt;heat&lt;/action&gt;. In 2 batches, &lt;action&gt;cook&lt;/action&gt; beef patties for 1-2 minutes each side until lightly charred and cooked through. Remove from &lt;action&gt;heat&lt;/action&gt; and keep warm. Repeat with remaining two patties.
3. Carefully &lt;action&gt;slice&lt;/action&gt; each burger bun into three acrossways, then lightly toast.
4. To assemble the burgers, spread a little Big Mac sauce over the bottom base. Top with some chopped onion, shredded lettuce, &lt;action&gt;slice&lt;/action&gt; of cheese, beef patty and some pickle slices. Top with the middle bun layer, and spread with more Big Mac sauce, onion, lettuce, pickles, beef patty and then finish with more sauce. Top with burger lid to serve.
5. After waiting half an hour for your food to settle, go for a jog.</instructions></recipe><recipe><id>52977</id><title>Corba</title><ingredients><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>cup Lentils</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>large Onion</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>large Carrots</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>tbs Tomato Puree</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>2</quantity><unit>tsp Cumin</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>tsp Paprika</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/2</quantity><unit>tsp Mint</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/2</quantity><unit>tsp Thyme</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/4</quantity><unit>tsp Black Pepper</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1/4</quantity><unit>tsp Red Pepper Flakes</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>4</quantity><unit>cups Vegetable Stock</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity>1</quantity><unit>cup Water</unit><item /></ingredient><ingredient><quantity /><unit>Pinch Sea Salt</unit><item>Pinch Sea Salt</item></ingredient></ingredients><instructions>Pick through your lentils for any foreign debris, rinse them 2 or 3 times, drain, and set aside.  Fair warning, this will probably turn your lentils into a solid block that you’ll have to break up later
In a large pot over medium-high &lt;action&gt;heat&lt;/action&gt;, sauté the olive oil and the onion with a pinch of salt for about 3 minutes, then &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; the carrots and &lt;action&gt;cook&lt;/action&gt; for another 3 minutes.
&lt;action&gt;Add&lt;/action&gt; the tomato paste and &lt;action&gt;stir&lt;/action&gt; it around for around 1 minute. Now &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; the cumin, paprika, mint, thyme, black pepper, and red pepper as quickly as you can and &lt;action&gt;stir&lt;/action&gt; for 10 seconds to bloom the spices. Congratulate yourself on how amazing your house now smells.
Immediately &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; the lentils, water, broth, and salt. Bring the soup to a (gentle) &lt;action&gt;boil&lt;/action&gt;.
After it has come to a &lt;action&gt;boil&lt;/action&gt;, reduce &lt;action&gt;heat&lt;/action&gt; to medium-low, cover the pot halfway, and &lt;action&gt;cook&lt;/action&gt; for 15-20 minutes or until the lentils have fallen apart and the carrots are completely cooked.
After the soup has cooked and the lentils are tender, blend the soup either in a blender or simply use a hand blender to reach the consistency you desire. Taste for seasoning and &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; more salt if necessary.
Serve with crushed-up crackers, torn up bread, or something else to &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; some extra thickness.  You could also use a traditional thickener (like cornstarch or flour), but I prefer to &lt;action&gt;add&lt;/action&gt; crackers for some texture and saltiness.  Makes great leftovers, stays good in the fridge for about a week.</instructions></recipe></recipes>